(The Underworld)
(Shen Yanlin)
♪Cruel world, where trust runs thin♪
(Ling Che)
♪Blades clash. Who will rise above?♪
(Shuangdao Hui)
♪Behind every smile, danger waits♪
(Dongshan Tai)
(Fei Liu)
♪Know your limits, know your worth♪
(Luo Song)
♪Stand strong against the raging tide♪
(Annie)
♪Ask how many times I've lost my way♪
♪Storms rage on the road to power♪
♪Let old promises fade into memory♪
♪Alone and fearless, I won't back down♪
♪Power is a crown forged in blood♪
♪Brotherhood is shelter from the storm♪
=The Underworld=
=Episode 16=
(Dongcheng Tiger)
Lin.
Where...
Where are you going?
Boss Che.
Stay with him for a while.
Lin...
I'll wait for you to come back.
Che...
(Loyalty)
Take me with you.
Fu, were you pretending to sleep?
No.
I was dreaming.
I'm going out
to get you some egg tarts.
Want some egg tarts?
Yes!
Then wait here for me, okay?
Okay.
(Dongcheng Tiger)
Egg tarts.
Che.
I want two.
Two.
Got it.
Be good.
Che's treating me to egg tarts.
This is Che's wallet.
Che...
Wangcai.
Che!
Che! Your wallet!
Wait!
Che! Che! Wait!
Che!
Your wallet!
Che! Che!
Che!
Officer Luo.
I wanted to ask about
the ecstasy found at the complex.
Any new leads?
We ran some tests.
It looks a lot like ecstasy,
but
it's a new drug called Yaba.
It contains methamphetamine.
We've never seen anything like it
in Shicheng before.
Any leads on your end?
Nothing yet.
I haven't found anything new.
But my gut tells me
Dongshan Tai is behind this somehow.
Cut back on the cigarettes.
And hurry.
Bad guy!
Che!
If we can find proof
that they're trafficking drugs,
we can push for
harsher sentences.
We can also
seriously weaken their operation.
I'll get on it.
Go. Hurry.
I-I'm not scared.
Protect Che.
There's a nail.
Pull it out.
Okay.
I'll handle it.
Che!
Run!
Stop!
Let me go investigate!
Calm down.
No!
Listen to me.
I want justice!
You can't go out there.
If you do, by tomorrow,
everyone will know
Dongcheng Gang's Ling Che
was meeting with the police here.
I don't care!
He may be Shen Yanlin's brother,
but he did nothing wrong.
He was a good man.
I got him killed.
Let me see him one last time.
Please let me see him one last time.
I understand. I understand.
Let me see him!
But
we've been working this case
for five years.
We can't give up now.
I'll take care of him.
We'll get him to a hospital.
Don't worry. He'll be fine.
He'll be okay.
Don't worry.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
It's okay. It's okay.
Relax. Relax.
Boss Lin.
(Morgue)
Boss Che.
I'd like to talk to my brother.
When I have money,
we'll
live in a big house.
We'll live like kings.
♪I have one wish♪
♪For us to see the same light♪
♪Though I've never seen it either♪
♪I think I know what it looks like♪
♪We're all the same♪
♪We were once lost and helpless kids♪
♪We've hit the walls of reality♪
♪We don't want to be covered in scars♪
♪Through ordinary days♪
♪I know that I'm♪
♪Not invincible♪
Fu.
It's been so long
since we really talked.
Fu.
You know,
since Boss Hui died,
I haven't slept well once.
Because I'm scared.
I'm scared that if I lose,
I'll end up like Boss Hui.
I'm scared.
I'm scared that if I'm gone someday,
I won't be there to protect you.
I'm scared that someday
you'll have no one to care for you.
♪I have one wish♪
♪For us to see the same light♪
♪Though I've never seen it either♪
♪I think I know what it looks like♪
But I never thought...
♪We're all the same♪
♪We were lost and helpless kids♪
you'd leave me first.
I shouldn't have yelled at you.
♪We don't want to be covered in scars♪
♪Through ordinary days♪
What have you ever protected me from?
I wanted to protect Lin.
♪And sometimes I'm still afraid♪
♪Sometimes lost, sometimes confused♪
Fu.
I'm sorry.
♪But I know♪
♪There's still a long hard road ahead♪
♪Look up♪
♪Gaze into the endless night♪
♪Believe a shooting star will streak by♪
♪And shine within your eyes♪
♪Open your arms♪
♪Embrace every pain you can't endure♪
Sleeping kids
raise their hands.
(And keep them raised.)
♪Our sky♪
Sleeping kids
raise their hands.
♪Through ordinary days♪
♪I know that I'm♪
♪Not invincible♪
♪And sometimes I'm still afraid♪
♪Sometimes lost, sometimes confused♪
♪Sometimes I don't know where I'm going♪
♪But I know♪
♪There's still a long hard road ahead♪
♪Look up♪
♪Gaze into the endless night♪
Fu.
I promise you.
I'll avenge you.
♪Embrace all the pain♪
I'll become the shot-caller.
♪And light up our sky♪
♪Our sky♪